fitness-superstore.co.uk 2013-12-24

# How To Order From Fitness Superstore

|  |  |   
---  
  
|   
---  
  
You have 5 methods to place your order! Telephone, mail, fax, online or in store at [any of our 9 Fitness Showrooms.](http://www.fitness-superstore.co.uk/showrooms/30003_i.html) All orders must be paid in full before they will be shipped.

  *  **Credit Card Orders** \- If you are ordering by credit card (mail order) the goods must be sent to the card holders registered address. If you require the goods to be sent elsewhere (ie a work address) you must telephone Fitness Superstore prior to ordering. You will be required to provide additional information
  *  **Telephone Orders** \- Telephone orders can be placed Monday to Friday 9.00am to 9.00pm, Saturday 9.00am to 5.00pm and Sunday 11.00am to 4.00pm. Have your order and credit card details ready. When placing your order by phone, you will be given an order number. Call us now on **01604 673000 6**
  *  **Mail Orders** \- If ordering by post you must provide all relevant information (ie product code and description, name and address, postcode and contact telephone numbers). Please allow 4 working days for clearance of personal cheques
  *  **Fax Orders** \- Fax the order to Fitness Superstore fax line 01604 673001. All faxed orders must be paid by credit/debit cards. We will call you to confirm receipt of your fax. You can fax your order 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, 365 days a year.
  *  **Internet Site Security** \- Fitness-Superstore.co.uk is 100% secure. Fitness Superstore guarantees the safety of your credit card information. All credit card information is handled with the utmost security and will never be released to any other organisation under any circumstance.

## To Guarantee Security we use SSL

Secure server technology, known as SSL (Secure Socket Layer). What this means is that when you place your order the details are encrypted before being sent. SSL encryption is virtually unbreakable. However if you still do not wish to send details via the internet you can place you order by calling or faxing us.

Fitness Superstore have never experienced any instance of credit card fraud resulting from information passed to us.  
  
## Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

 **To process transactions**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

 **To send periodic emails**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please click on the unsubscribe link and follow the instructions.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
  
#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions section](http://www.fitness-superstore.co.uk/tandcs/30102_i.html) establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on **16/03/2009**

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Bodypower Sports Plc  
13 Gate Lodge Close   
Round Spinney  
Northampton  
NN3 8RJ  
United Kingdom  
01604 673000  
  
|   
---  
Your basket is currently empty  

  * A-G (34 brands)
    * Adidas
    * Animal
    * Back Office
    * Baden
    * BBE
    * Best Fitness
    * BH Fitness
    * Body Sculpture
    * Body-Solid
    * Bodycore
    * Bodypower
    * Bodypower UK
    * Bosu
    * Bowflex
    * Boxing-Mad
    * BPI
    * Bremshey
    * Butterfly
    * Concept II
    * Cornilleau
    * CytoSport
    * Eleiko
    * Everlast
    * FAS
    * First Degree
    * Fitness-MAD
    * Fitness-Superstore
    * FKPro
    * Forward Foods
    * Fuel
    * Gaspari
    * GoFit
    * Golds Gym
    * Grenade
  * H-N (16 brands)
    * Hammer Strength
    * High Street TV
    * Horizon
    * Hyper Strength
    * Johnson
    * Kettler
    * Life Fitness
    * Louisville Slugger
    * Marcy
    * Matrix Fitness
    * Maximuscle
    * Mightymast
    * Monster Milk
    * MyProtein
    * NordicTrack
    * Nutrisport
  * O-S (28 brands)
    * Octane
    * Optimum Nutrition
    * P.C. XF
    * PharmaFreak
    * Pilates-MAD
    * Polar
    * Power Plate
    * Powerbag
    * Powerblock 
    * Powerline
    * Powertec
    * Precor
    * Pro-Form
    * Prospot Fitness
    * Proteus
    * PVL
    * Reebok
    * Reflex Nutrition
    * Relay Fitness
    * Rug Runner
    * Schwinn
    * Scitec
    * Sigma
    * Slam Man
    * Spirit
    * Stairmaster
    * Sure Shot
    * Syntrax
  * T-Z (17 brands)
    * TKO
    * Torque Fitness
    * Trixter
    * Tunturi
    * U.S.N.
    * UFC
    * USP
    * Vectra
    * Vibro Gym
    * Vision Fitness
    * Waterrower
    * Wave Rower
    * Web Racer
    * Weider
    * Weslo
    * Yoga-MAD
    * York 

  * Body-Solid
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Accessories
      * Crossfit Equipment
    * Gym Equipment
      * Benches
      * Leverage Systems
      * Multi-Gyms
      * Power Cages & Racks
      * Smith Machines
      * Leg Machines
      * Arm Machines
      * Dumbbells & Kettlebells
      * Accessories
      * Back Machines
      * Abdo Machines
      * Chest & Shoulder Machines
      * Cable Machines
      * VKR/Dip Stations
      * Storage Racks
      * Weight Plates & Barbell Sets
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
      * Full Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Gym Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
      * Christmas Gifts
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Multi Gym
      * Gym Equipment
      * Weight Benches
  * Bodypower
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Accessories
      * Crossfit Equipment
    * Gym Equipment
      * Multi-Gyms
      * Dumbbells & Kettlebells
      * Accessories
      * Abdo Machines
      * Storage Racks
      * Weight Plates & Barbell Sets
    * Boxing Equipment
      * Accessories
      * Punch Bags
      * Free Standing Punch Bags/Man
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
      * Full Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Gym Equipment Sale
      * Boxing Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
      * Christmas Gifts
    * Sports Nutrition
      * Protein Supplements
      * Weight Loss Supplements
      * Creatine Supplements
      * Supplement Bundles
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Boxing Equipment
      * Nutrition
      * Fitness Accessories
      * Weights And Bars
      * Dumbbells And Kettlebells
  * First Degree
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Upper Body Trainers
      * Rowing Machines
      * Accessories
      * Crossfit Equipment
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
      * Full Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Exercise Bike
      * Rowing Machine
      * Fitness Accessories
  * Horizon
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Rowing Machines
      * Treadmills
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
      * Christmas Gifts
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Treadmill
      * Cross Trainer
      * Exercise Bike
      * Rowing Machine
  * Kettler
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Rowing Machines
      * Steppers
      * Accessories
      * Treadmills
    * Gym Equipment
      * Multi-Gyms
    * Sports Equipment
      * Heart Rate Monitors
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
      * Christmas Gifts
    * Table Tennis Tables
      * Outdoor Table Tennis Tables
      * Indoor Table Tennis Tables
      * Table Tennis Accessories
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Treadmill
      * Cross Trainer
      * Exercise Bike
  * Life Fitness
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Accessories
      * Treadmills
    * Gym Equipment
      * Benches
      * Leverage Systems
      * Multi-Gyms
      * Power Cages & Racks
      * Smith Machines
      * Leg Machines
      * Arm Machines
      * Back Machines
      * Abdo Machines
      * Chest & Shoulder Machines
      * Cable Machines
      * VKR/Dip Stations
      * Storage Racks
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
      * Full Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Multi Gym
  * NordicTrack
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Treadmills
    * Gym Equipment
      * Benches
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
      * Christmas Gifts
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Treadmill
      * Cross Trainer
      * Exercise Bike
  * Octane
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Elliptical Trainers
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
      * Full Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
  * Power Plate
    * Power Plates
  * Powertec
    * Gym Equipment
      * Benches
      * Leverage Systems
      * Power Cages & Racks
      * Leg Machines
      * Back Machines
      * Chest & Shoulder Machines
      * VKR/Dip Stations
      * Storage Racks
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Gym Equipment
  * Precor
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Treadmills
    * Gym Equipment
      * Benches
      * Multi-Gyms
      * Cable Machines
  * Vision Fitness
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Treadmills
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Treadmill
      * Cross Trainer
      * Exercise Bike
  * York 
    * Fitness Equipment
      * Exercise Bikes
      * Elliptical Trainers
      * Rowing Machines
      * Accessories
      * Treadmills
      * Crossfit Equipment
    * Gym Equipment
      * Benches
      * Power Cages & Racks
      * Leg Machines
      * Arm Machines
      * Dumbbells & Kettlebells
      * Accessories
      * Back Machines
      * Abdo Machines
      * VKR/Dip Stations
      * Storage Racks
      * Weight Plates & Barbell Sets
    * Boxing Equipment
      * Accessories
      * Punch Bags
      * Stands and Brackets
      * Medicine Balls
    * Commercial Equipment
      * Light Commercial
      * Full Commercial
    * Special Offers
      * Fitness Equipment Sale
      * Ex-Demo/Returns
      * Christmas Gifts
    * Table Tennis Tables
      * Table Tennis Accessories
    * SALE NOW ON
      * Treadmill
      * Cross Trainer
      * Exercise Bike
      * Rowing Machine
      * Multi Gym
      * Boxing Equipment
      * Gym Equipment
      * Weight Benches
      * Fitness Accessories
      * Weights And Bars
